A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Economic Reform Interests, Series F FA315
Rockefeller Archive Center
- New York City Building Zone Law, 1916-1942 (Box 18, Folder 148)
- New York Stock Exchange, 1901-1958 (Box 18, Folder 149)
  Routine correspondence. John D. Rockefeller's sale of 1/4 of seat in 1929; Laurance S. Rockefeller purchased John D. Rockefeller's seat in 1937. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller.
  102
- New York Stock Exchange, 1901-1958 (Box 18, Folder 150)
- Personal Relations in Industry, 1923-1928 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  Ivy Lee and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. discuss propriety of proposed publisher; reasons for selection. Preparation of book; distribution of book; royalties received. Copy of book; comments on book; acknowledgements; Cornell Speech, 1917.
  201
- Personal Relations in Industry, 1923-1928 (Box 19, Folder 152)
- Personal Relations in Industry, 1923-1928 (Box 19, Folder 153)
- Personal Relations in Industry, 1923-1928 (Box 19, Folder 154)
- Personal Relations in Industry - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Book - Publication, 1923-1930 (Box 19, Folder 155)
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Radio Talk, February 12, 1928, 1928-1939 (Box 19, Folder 156)
  Preparation, clippings, comments. 14 copies of speech. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John B. Kennedy.
  194
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Radio Talk, February 12, 1928 - Letters of Appreciation (Box 19, Folder 157)
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Radio Talk, February 12, 1928 - Letters of Appreciation (Box 19, Folder 158)
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Radio Address, 1937, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 159)
  Request to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to make address on unemployment census; proposed text. Address; results of census. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  167
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Radio Address, 1937 - Letters of Appreciation (Box 19, Folder 160)
- Reconstruction, 1919-1926 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  Labor, management, social, political efforts in 1919-1920 "Red Scare" period. Some of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s thinking on topics such as labor unions, his relation to them, importance of changing prices and wages, the need for cooperation during a period of stress, etc. reflected. Correspondents include Sam Gompers, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  226
- Reconstruction - American Alliance for Labor and Democracy, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 162)
- Reconstruction Commission of the State of New York, 1919 (Box 19, Folder 163)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contribution of $500.
- Reconstruction - Leonard P. Ayers Article on Price Changes, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 164)
- Reconstruction - American War-Community Services, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 19, Folder 165)
  Request for support declined. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Reconstruction - Joint Conference, 1918-1919 (Box 19, Folder 166)
  Joint conference between the New York Chamber of Commerce and New York State Federation of Labor.
- Reconstruction - Community Councils, 1918-1959 (Box 19, Folder 167)
  Defense organizations at local level in 1918; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed $500. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $700 to Council unemployment agency, 1919. Branched into playground, town meeting work; no later Rockefeller interest. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, Arthur W. Packard.
  226.1
- Reconstruction - Community Councils, 1918-1959 (Box 19, Folder 168)
- Representation in Industry - General Correspondence - Miscellaneous Articles, 1918-1940 (Box 20, Folder 169)
  General correspondence, A. C. Bedford's request to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to make speech, King and Lee urge John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to accept. Requests to publish excerpts, Publication. Miscellaneous industrial articles. Letters of acknowledgement. Correspondents include W. L. MacKenzie King, L. L. Lee, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  225
- Representation in Industry (A-B), 1918-1940 (Box 20, Folder 170)
- Representation in Industry (C-D), 1918-1940 (Box 20, Folder 171)
- Representation in Industry (E-G), 1918-1940 (Box 20, Folder 172)
- Representation in Industry (H-L), 1918-1940 (Box 20, Folder 173)
- Representation in Industry (M-R), 1918-1940 (Box 20, Folder 174)
- Representation in Industry (S-Z), 1918-1940 (Box 20, Folder 175)
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Joint Legislative Committee to Investigate Public Service Commission, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 176)
  List of corporations in which John D. Rockefeller, Jr. had financial interests. (1916) Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Charles O. Heydt, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  170
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Emergency Employment Committee, 1930-1932 (Box 21, Folder 177)
  Appointment of committee to collect funds for emergency employment in New York City. Letters of thanks for John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gift to committee; newspaper clippings. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Charles O. Heydt, W. S. Gifford, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Emergency Employment Committee - Pledge, January 26, 1931 - Girls and Women Relief, 1931-1932 (Box 21, Folder 178)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledge to fund for use in caring for unemployed women and girls; conditions of pledge. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Cornelius Bliss, Eleanor R. Belmont.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Emergency Employment Committee - Pledge - November 10, 1930, 1931-1932 (Box 21, Folder 179)
  John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. joint contribution to work of Committee. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, C. Bliss, Seward Prosser, Phillip Keebler.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Brooklyn Unemployment Emergency Committee, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 180)
  Work of the committee; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledge; declination of contribution to Queens. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, George A. Wingate.
  170.1
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Harlem Committee on Relief and Unemployment, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 181)
  Work of the Committee; conditions confronting people in Harlem. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledge to "make work" and direct relief activities. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Arthur Woods.
  170.2
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Miscellaneous Plans, 1931-1935 (Box 21, Folder 182)
  Solving unemployment and relief needs in Westchester County. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pleasure at reading Adelbert Ames Jr.'s pamphlet "Progress and Prosperity." Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  170.3
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Miscellaneous Plans - Samuel S. Wyer, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 183)
  Wyer's social-engineering activities.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Miscellaneous Plans - Home Mortgage Advisory Board, 1932-1936 (Box 21, Folder 184)
  Organization of Committee, John D. Rockefeller 3rd's membership. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Frank A. Vanderlip.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Miscellaneous Plans - James H. Rand - Correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 21, Folder 185)
  Rand Plan for putting three million people back to work on February 1, 1933; publications of the Committee for the Nation. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., James H. Rand, Jr., R. E. Wood.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Miscellaneous Plans - Mobilization of Human Needs, 1932-1934 (Box 21, Folder 186)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines invitation to serve on National Citizens Committee for health reasons. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Newton D. Baker, J. S. Bryan, Charles P. Taft.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Unemployment Relief, 1931-1936 (Box 21, Folder 187)
  Printed materials; reports on unemployment in New York City; plans for dinner to open Emergency Unemployment Relief Campaign. Data on number of men employed at Fort Tryon, Claremont Park, Rockefeller Center. John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledge toward unemployment fund. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Thomas M. Debevoise, Raymond B. Fosdick, Harvey D. Gibson.
  170.4
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Unemployment Relief - Architect's Emergency Committee, 1932-1934 (Box 21, Folder 188)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution to Committee; work of committee. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Amey Aldrich.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Unemployment Relief - Block-Aiders, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 189)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd's work with Block Community Organization Campaign. Mr. and Mrs. Prentice's contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Unemployment Relief - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Gift, 1931, 1931-1932 (Box 21, Folder 190)
  John D. Rockefeller 3rd pledge to Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Unemployment Relief - Seamen's Welfare Agencies, 1932-1933 (Box 21, Folder 191)
  Work of committee aiding stranded sailors in port of New York. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Charles S. Haight, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Unemployment Relief - Actors, Authors, and Artists Relief, 1933-1936 (Box 21, Folder 192)
  Work of the Committee; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution to Authors League Fund, Drama Committee, and Stage Relief Fund. Correspondents include Ivy Lee, Arthur W. Packard, Louise Sillcox, Frank Gillman, Ashley Miller.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Unemployment Relief - Hop Light Ladies, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 193)
  Work of the Hop Light Ladies; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution to program. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, M. Alberta Hublit.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 194)
  Plans for luncheon meeting to raise New York emergency relief fund; Rockefeller Foundation pledge to Emergency Unemployment Committee. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., H. D. Gibson, Irwin S. Cobb.
  170.41
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee - Tarrytown Situation, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 195)
  Work of Mayor's Committee on Unemployment Relief in Tarrytown; unemployment conditions in Tarrytown. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s offer of fund to North Tarrytown and Mt. Pleasant for highway construction; earmarking of Christmas gift fund from Pocantico Hills Estate to needy in Tarrytown, North Tarrytown, and Mt. Pleasant, through County Welfare Board, Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, D. R. DeLap, Robert W. Gumbel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee - Newspaper Clippings, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 196)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s letters of thanks to editors for favorable treatment of gift to unemployment fund.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee - Gibson Committee Campaign Material, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 197)
  Unemployment relief for 1932-1933 winter; work of committee. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Rockefeller Foundation contributions. Correspondents include H. D. Gibson, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas Cochran.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Musicians Emergency Fund, 1932-1961 (Box 22, Folder 198)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributes $10,000 toward unemployed musicians in 1932; Nelson A. Rockefeller declines to serve on committees. Smaller contributions by several members of the family made in later years; Mary French Rockefeller a sustaining member. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mary French Rockefeller, Walter Damrosch.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Musicians Emergency Fund, 1932-1961 (Box 22, Folder 199)
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Hospitalized Veterans Music Service, 1946-1961 (Box 22, Folder 200)
  Work in hospitals; financed music lessons for veterans. Winthrop Rockefeller interested as part of his study of veterans rehabilitation; no John D. Rockefeller, Jr. interest. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Winthrop Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  170.411
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Hospitalized Veterans Music Service - Contributions, 1957-1961 (Box 22, Folder 201)
  Mary French Rockefeller made contributions ranging from $100 to $1,000.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Hospitalized Veterans Music Service - Contributions, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 201A)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted material.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - National Recovery Act, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 202)
  Code requirements affecting Rockefeller employees. Correspondents include Robert W. Gumbel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  170.5
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - National Recovery Act - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Speech, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 203)
  Text of radio address, August 26, 1933. Letters received regarding speech. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Citizen's Family Welfare Committee, 1934-1953 (Box 22, Folder 204)
  Invitations to John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller to become members of Special Gifts Committee; John D. Rockefeller 3rd and Nelson A. Rockefeller contributions, granting of permission to quote from November 16, 1933 address by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include J. G> Blaine, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  170.6
- Unemployment and Economic Planning - Citizen's Family Welfare Committee - Nelson A. Rockefeller Correspondence - Special Gift Committee, 1933-1934 (Box 22, Folder 205)
  Campaign for funds by Family Welfare Committee of New York City, plans for division of amounts raised among family welfare agencies, contributions by persons encouraged to do so by Nelson A. Rockefeller. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, J. G. Blaine, Henry Harkness Flagler, Charles C. Huitt, David Sarnoff, F. LaGuardia.
- United States Industrial Commission - Correspondence, 1900-1937 (Box 23, Folder 206)
  Calling of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Sr., Ivy Lee, J. F. Welborn and E. H. Weitzel to stand, in 1915. Character of F. P. Walsh, chairman of committee. Collection of information regarding Colorado Fuel & Iron strike; General Education Board and Foundation. Arranging time of hearing; comments on testimony received by commission by various people.
  26
- United States Industrial Commission - Correspondence, 1900-1937 (Box 23, Folder 207)
- United States Industrial Commission - Correspondence - Committee on Industrial Relations, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 208)
- United States Industrial Commission - Correspondence - General - Newspaper Comment, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 209)
  26A
- United States Industrial Commission - Correspondence, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 210)
- United States Industrial Commission - Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 23, Folder 211)
  26B
- United States Industrial Commission - Correspondence - Testimony of John D. Rockefeller, Sr., 1900 (Box 23, Folder 212)
  1900 investigation into trusts by similar commission; John D. Rockefeller testified.
- United States Industrial Commission - Hearing - Testimony and Statement, 1914-1915 (Box 23, Folder 213)
  Testimony by Mr. Weitzel, Judge Ben Lindsey, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Answers to questions regarding Rockefeller Foundation.
- United States Industrial Commission - Hearing - Testimony and Statement - Information Furnished by the Rockefeller Foundation, 1914-1915 (Box 23, Folder 214)
  26C
- United States Industrial Commission - Hearing - Testimony and Statement - E. H. Weitzel, December 8-9, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 215)
  26D
- United States Industrial Commission - Hearing - Testimony and Statement - Dr. William H. Allen, February 6, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 216)
  26E
- United States Industrial Commission - Hearing - Testimony and Statement - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., May 20-21, 1915; 2 copies (Box 23, Folder 217)
  26F
- United States Industrial Commission - Testimony of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Given Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), January 25-26, May 20-22, 1915; Copy 1 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 0217A)
- United States Industrial Commission - Testimony of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Given Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), January 25-26, May 20-22, 1915; Copy 2 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 0217B)
- United States Industrial Commission - Statements of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), January 25, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 0217C)
- United States Industrial Commission - Statements of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), May 20-21, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 217)
- United States Industrial Commission - Statements of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), May 20-21, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 0217E)
- United States Industrial Commission - Testimony of Ivy L. Lee Given Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), January 27-28, May 22, 25, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 217)
- United States Industrial Commission - Testimony of E. H. Weitzel Given Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), December 8-9, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 0217G)
- United States Industrial Commission - Testimony of J. F. Welborn Given Before the United States Commission on Industrial Relations (USCIR), December 4-7, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 0217H)
- United States Industrial Commission - Information Furnished by the Rockefeller Foundation in Response to Questionnaires (Box 24, Folder 0217I)
- United States Industrial Commission - Letters Supplied to the United States Commission on Industrial Relations by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Colorado Fuel & Iron (Box 24, Folder 0217J)
- United States Industrial Commission - Final Report of Commission on Industrial Relations, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 0217K)
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Official Guide Book (Box 25, Folder 0217L)
  235
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - General (Box 25, Folder 218)
  Nelson A. Rockefeller accepts offer as member of Board of Incorporators after John D. Rockefeller, Jr. refuses. Planning the fair; invitations to members of the family to participation in activities. Promotion of Rockefeller Center. Problems of fair; liquidation. Correspondents include Grover Whelan, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - General (Box 25, Folder 219)
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - General (Box 25, Folder 220)
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Correspondence, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 221)
  Served on Far East committee. Nothing here. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Hospitality Committee - National Advisory Committee, 1939-1941 (Box 25, Folder 222)
  Rockefeller contributions, membership in Hospitality organization to care for distinguished visitors to Fair. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - League of Nations Building, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 223)
  Nothing except fact of John D. Rockefeller 3rd's interest. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Terrace Club, 1938-1941 (Box 25, Folder 224)
  For those who bought over $5,000 in Fair bonds; Laurance S. Rockefeller did. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Paintings Loaned, 1939-1941 (Box 25, Folder 225)
  Four paintings from apartment loaned to Art exhibit at Fair. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. paid insurance on them; loaned 2 pictures second year. Project underwritten by Miss Margaret DeQuevas. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller Jr.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Subscription for Bonds, 1936-1941 (Box 25, Folder 226)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. subscribes for $250,000; then a second $250,000. Laurance S. Rockefeller subscribes $5,000. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. sold bonds at loss. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Petroleum Industry Executives (PIE) Roof, Inc. (Petroleum Building), 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 227)
  Rockefeller membership in roof club at fair for petroleum industry executives. No significant information here.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Temple of Religion, Inc., 1937-1941 (Box 26, Folder 228)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s support of temple; restricted to New York Fair efforts; support of temple.
  235.3
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Temple of Religion, Inc. - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Address, November 9, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 229)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s address. Copy here. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Temple of Religion, Inc. - Contributions, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 230)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution toward Temple; offers to raise fund for project. Money sent to him forwarded to Fair organization. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. writes appeal letters for contribution to Fair; John D. Rockefeller 3rd also solicits. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Temple of Religion, Inc. - Contributions, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 231)
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - York Yachts, Inc., 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 0231A)
  Laurance S. Rockefeller invests in scheme for ferry service from midtown Manhattan to Fair site. Membership plan to guarantee expenses; membership drive. Small traffic. Financial troubles. Laurance S. Rockefeller resigns as director; new company formed. Nelson A. Rockefeller a member of club. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Leonard Outhwaite.
  235.4
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - York Yachts, Inc. - Laurance S. Rockefeller Mortgage and Sale of Boats, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 0231B)
  Laurance S. Rockefeller handled liquidation of boats.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - York Yachts, Inc. - Laurance S. Rockefeller Stock Interest and Notes, 1939-1942 (Box 26, Folder 0231C)
  Investment in York Yachts, Inc.
- New York World's Fair, 1939 - Opening of Exhibits and Fair, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 232)
  Invitations to Rockefellers to various openings. Use of Rockefeller Yacht for Venezuelan visitors. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  235.5
- Brussels World's Fair, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 233)
  Appeals for support of several United States activities at fair; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contribution toward Protestant pavilion. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Dana S. Creel.
  237
  DR material removed to Folder 233A.
- Brussels World's Fair, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 0233A)
- National Trade Policy - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 234)
  Organized to promote a sound foreign economic policy, including tariff reductions. John D. Rockefeller 3rd interest. Comments on activities. John D. Rockefeller 3rd correspondence with congressmen over reciprocal trade agreements. Reports of committee. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel, Frank Jamieson.
  54
  DR material removed to Folder 234A.
- National Trade Policy - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 0234A)
  David Rockefeller 1953 contribution. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
- National Trade Policy - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1953-1961 (Box 27, Folder 235)
  DR material removed to Folder 235C.